<html><p>I heard that there's a treasure out there buried in the snow. The thing is, no one wants to go look for it with all those undead out there moaning and groaning and stumbling around.</p><p>But you look like someone who can take care of themselves! Why don't you go poke around and see if you can find anything. I hear it's to the north. I bet it's pretty valuable if someone took the time to hide it on this forsaken allod.</p></html>