<html><p>Remember, fool, only the gods or forces equal to gods can destroy gods. And you, parasites, are abusing this force! "Patrons"... what a joke. Yet another lie is all it is. Couldn't you at least lie with dignity...</p><p>There were no Patrons. Or, more to the point, all of your mages croaked in the Cataclysm. Croaked, and that was that. And the floods that you and yours use so brazenly - I created those! First I gave some of my power to the dragons, but those brainless lizards wasted it left and right, weakening all the while. The power left them like wine through a sieve. Predictably, they were left weak and vulnerable... Of which the Junes took advantage, mowing them down almost to the last. Then I traded in the dolt dragons for Seals: concentrated power meant for a single purpose - keeping Sarn imprisoned. If it hadn't been for your Cataclysm, the whole thing might have lasted for quite a while. Luckily for Sarn and unluckily for us, catastrophe befell the Seals, and part of their power was lost to the astral. Part of my power!</p><p>The dragon's power, the remnants of which were utilized by your mages, and the power of the Seals, which you are using now while calling it Patronage - all of this power came from me! Do you really think that you can destroy me with my own weapons?</p><p>Frankly, I'm not even offended by your actions. Moreover, I would have thought less of your bravery and ambition if you hadn't challenged me. But I must say you picked the wrong time to interfere. You still can't use the Gates, no matter how hard you try. Tell your Yasker that I said he can go get bent! As for you, we'll see each other again!</p></html>