<html><p>Each soldier of the Empire wears a medallion blessed by the Trinity Church. These beacons of light cannot be allowed to descend into darkness. We must not allow the servants of Tep to twist to their own dark uses.</p><p>We have eight warriors unaccounted for since the day those damn cultists appeared. Go to the catacombs beneath the Hadron Quarter and retrieve their missing medallions from the undead. May the Light protect you!</p></html>