<html><p>Yes, I saw what you did from atop this tower. It was a very convincing speech, but I believe I detected a slight tremor in your voice as you read out that lie. Now, I know that the world is changing. We now have more important things to do than fight the Empire. It might be time to unite, as we once did during the Great Astral Campaign.</p><p>However, the war has been a great blessing to our people. It has united all three races of the League and motivated many of our actions. But it seems like its usefulness might be at an end.</p><p>We could achieve more if we were at peace. We could spend our time creating works of art, enjoying life and relaxing, and appreciating the traditions of our people. The League has a great future indeed - and it is not tied to the battlefield.</p><p>Maybe if the demons were to be made our new enemy, our people would stop believing that we cannot exist without our war against the Empire. War is a poor stimulant when compared to other alternatives. It must be replaced.</p><p>Perhaps we could spend more time researching the mysteries of the past. After all, the Zem, the June, and even the dragons have many things to teach us. We simply have to look for those truths. And in doing so, we might find something else to unite us all.</p><p>At the moment, I am not yet ready to act upon these thoughts. However, I will think about them quite deeply. Maybe one day it will be time to put this plan into action.</p></html>