<html>Access only by permission from Negus Tot! Forbidden to unauthorized personnel!<br/>What? Negus Tot sent you? He even said "modernized crocodile"?! How dare he!<br/>Very well, I'll deal with him later. What do you want to know? We value every minute here.<br/>So, the Spark of a slain one is stuck in the Purgatory? And that poor soul died here, in the crypt? Hmm... Damnation! I shouldn't have used Master's weapon...<br/>What terrible luck! I thought that we did everything perfectly, but now I find out that some curious bastard died and appeared in the Purgatory... That's bad, very bad. Now I won't be able to transport Master's valuable equipment quietly. Well... As they say, nothing personal, just business! Master will make use of your Spark as well!</html>