<html>How can we get in touch with Novogard, eh? We have no Adventurer's Stones, and teleport spells aren't working. Even the elven master who was on board of the flagship only shrugs his wings and mutters something queer about distortions in astral channels and displacement of some kind of nodes. I guess we're stuck deep here... Oh, whatever will we do? We may have to utilize that secret elven invention. I just hope it doesn't break down...<br/>Here, take it. This thing is called a long-range communicator. It was made by elves! If they're telling the truth, we can use it to get in touch with any sorcerer in Sarnaut. However, it's only charged enough to last two minutes.<br/>Well then, let's try contacting Aidenus.</html>