<html><p>Prophetic Cards are a valuable item. If you are lucky enough, they will reward you generously.</p><p>But the cards themselves will not reveal their treasures. In order to decipher them and receive your prizes, you should buy an Ancient Compass from the Item Shop. You may also choose to delve deeper into the secrets of the cards by using more compasses to receive additional rewards. Your chances of winning a better prize increase with each attempt.</p></html>