<html><p>Attention, attention!</p><p>Hear Yasker's new order.</p><p>"The Imperial Army has long been proud of its skilled and disciplined soldiers. Now that there is a war raging furiously in the Holy Land, everyone capable of wielding a sword or using magic should devote their utmost attention to perfecting their combat skills.</p><p>The best Imperial trainers are willing to assist you with learning all of the techniques you need to know. Hurry and learn what you can!"</p><p>Did you hear that? Do you know what needs to be done? Good.</p><p>The warrior trainer, Sledge the Rowdy, is waiting for you in Yasker's Tower. She'll show you how to hold your weapon straight and deliver mighty blows. Enjoy!</p></html>