<html><p>Those ghostly boars look harmless enough, but when they surrounded us they knocked us down and tore at us with their fangs! We barely escaped and our clothes were in rags.</p><p>Now we walk around with our shields at the ready wherever we go, but with ragged boots barely covering our feet. If only we could visit the busy city and find a crafty leather worker to make us a pair of birch sandals...</p></html>