<html>Oh, the comms are down... Whatever will we do? Think, my dear brain, think...<br/>Bingo! I got an idea! Clement, a scientist from House de Ardeur, mentioned something about stone ruins not far from the camp. He said they looked like a portal and have been there since the June era. However, it was non-functional when we checked it. We'd kick and rub it, and the elf would cast all kinds of spells - it just wouldn't work. But we didn't have an Adventurer's Stone, which you do! All Stones are linked to portals, we know that for sure. What if your Stone can awaken the portal?<br/>Trying costs nothing, after all. Go see Clement and try doing something about that goddamned portal. What exactly? How should I know?! Bang your head against it or strike it with your Stone!<br/>Get creative! Actually, that's not a bad idea. No, not the one about the head! I'm talking about the Stone. Perhaps contacting the magic slumbering inside the ruins can awaken them, eh? That would be great!</html>