<html><p>Damn it! We've been tricked! Those scumbag vampires figured out that we were planning on using the artifact and charged it with dark energy! Not only does the artifact's magic no longer help repel the destructive beam, it amplifies it!</p><p>That's a real shame about the artifact - it was one of a kind. But we're out of time! I will not be able to hold back the beam for long. Our allod is doomed!</p><p>Tell Yaver Meryatum that the Historians must evacuate immediately. I will stay behind and hold back the beam for as long as I can so that all of you can escape!</p></html>