<html><p>The thicket has been teeming with panthers and tigers lately! And those damn cats have taken a liking to munching on the soldiers from our camp. That's right - they're man-eaters now!</p><p>The three of us dug a trench to trap them, but those cunning beasts just walked around it. But then the commander fell right in and broke his leg! We got in pretty big trouble for that. We don't know what else to do now...</p><p>Please help us thin the panthers' and the tigers' numbers some before they turn our entire camp into their cafeteria.</p></html>