<html><p>Skirmishes are an excellent opportunity to earn glory, honor, and respect and to acquire unique equipment and powerful weapons.</p><p>The goal is to capture and maintain control over points in key areas. For example, at Witch's Hollow these points are the windmill, the sawmill, and the old ruins. To take these key points, you must raise your teams banner nearby and prevent your opponents from raising theirs.</p><p>You will collect the resources extracted from these structures for as long as you can hold onto them. The first team to collect the required amount of resources is the winner. It's simple!</p></html>