<html><p>There's no doubt about it, the Freeborn are to blame. They're a group of all sorts of rabble - goblins, satyrs, and tons of other mischievous creatures! They have to be working with the mafia, and they should have been put in their place a long time ago!</p><p>Unfortunately we were ordered not to interfere with any matters that aren't proven to be part of the sea salt trafficking. Even then, we must keep our true identities a secret. In other words, we don't exist and we must let the Freeborn believe they are the bosses of the seabed.</p><p>I guess the Council knows what's best, but I think I can figure out a way to bend the rules a little. Let's do it like this. Take these notices from Rodion Borodin. Listen to what they say.</p><p>"The Empire is looking for anyone who has information, rumors, or even thoughts about who, when, how, or for what reason construction is going on to the east of the Mana Station. They will be well rewarded for their help."</p><p>Post them up around the Freeborn headquarters at Pridonsk. If any of them take the bait and report to Borodin with information, we'll know straight away that they've been hanging around the sea salt flats to the south. That will prove their guilt!</p></html>