<html><p>Look, I'm working on a highly classified project that I cannot reveal too many details on. What I can tell you is that the experiments were conducted on existing zombies.</p><p>Early test results were moving along according to plan, however, the zombies began to disappear and we started to lose track on a number of our test subjects.</p><p>Eventually, the zombies reappeared and were actually quite aggressive. At this point it would actually be more troublesome for me to devise some sort of procedure to calm down their aggression - it would be much more efficient if you could destroy the zombies for me.</p><p>Ah, one more thing, I need the amulets the zombies were carrying as they were also part of the experiment.</p></html>