<html><p>Now that you've decided that you want to be an alchemist, we shouldn't waste any time with your training! Bring me ten stain removers. It's a relatively easy task, so it really shouldn't be a problem for you.</p><p>What? You're afraid it might be too easy? Don't worry, every great alchemist has to start somewhere. Once you complete this task it'll be clear to us both that you are ready to travel down the path of an alchemist. I'm sure you'll learn more difficult recipes along the way.</p></html>