<html><p>Say, can I trust you? Hmm... I guess I can, you have an honest face. Well, I'm new here, and I'm looking for friends. You see, I recently escaped from Brazen Hill. I was being persecuted endlessly due to my family's fall from grace. Then those rookies from Umoira started giving me all kinds of trouble so I left.</p><p>I heard you could make a ton of money by selling dark artifacts here. It's a lie! I spent a week toiling in the Rusted Wasteland and then when I returned I could hardly sell them! The only things valued around here are trinkets from beyond the Cordon. Which means that I'm still broke...</p><p>To top it all off, care to venture a guess as to how much the Free Traders wanted for a bag and a pick so I could even get started? An arm and a leg!</p><p>I've got an idea that'll get me back on my feet, but I'll need some help. You see, I overheard an interesting tidbit earlier - a wagon is headed to the post on the Northern Border with artifacts from beyond the Cordon. Why don't the two of us rob it?! That'll solve all our problems!</p><p>Don't get nervous, it really is a safe bet. I'll tell you exactly where to set up the ambush - just get in, kill the guards, grab the artifacts, and get out! Oh, and put on this disguise before you do it! So, how about it?</p></html>