<html>Strictly Confidential.<br/>Attn: Agent Smith.<br/>Welcome back to service, Agent Smith!<br/>You may not remember your past life as an agent, since we had to remove a part of your memory in order to avoid your disclosure.<br/>We were forced to use this unusual means of communication as the magnetic storms in the astral and the space-time distortion prevented us from contacting you in a regular manner. The news we are to deliver is very urgent: your mission on establishing our world domination using a powerful virtual reality modulator codenamed Allods Online now enters its second stage. Your are entrusted to distribute a secret program masked as a new promo clip to bend all its viewers to our will. <br/>Your task is to specify your account in any of the supported social networks in the Settings menu, then visit the page of our official community and share a new video review on your profile page. Finally, you must activate the Extraterrestrial Transmitter (enclosed) to inform us that the mission is completed.<br/>Stepan Orlov will be your courier. When you finish, meet him to get the parcel with the concealment clothing that will protect you from possible shadows. Good luck, Agent!</html>