<html><p>A letter from Pierre? Hm, news of more trouble... All sorts of problems have started here lately. The Galleon, built for us by the de Ardeur architects, was attacked during the night by some strange creatures. We had to flee here, to Summer Manor. We've lost everything!</p><p>Wait, let me gather my thoughts. What was your mission? Oh, yes, the sculptor from the rebellious House de Doucer... What did you find out?</p><p>You witnessed a ritual that created an Astral creature, and Raoul participated in it?! Wow! That's very interesting! We were attacked by strange Astral creatures - maybe they're related.</p><p>They are similar to spiders, bats, and rats in appearance but they have different abilities. We call them mutants at the moment, for want of a better name. They are very dangerous, so be careful when roaming this allod!</p><p>Well, it's clear that there is a link between our troubles and the events in Darkwater... Don't go anywhere, I'm going to need your help if we're to fix this mess.</p></html>