<html><p>I can't stay here anymore! It's so dark, always dark... The fog seems to seep into my bones... Twilight everywhere, endless dark... You can't tell night from day. Damn this ghostly allod!</p><p>Imperial citizens are lucky. The Arisen are said to have created special mana lanterns that can dispel the darkness. They say that they're rare, though, even in Nezebgrad... Are they real or is it just a story?</p></html>