<html><p>We showed them again! They're done for! And we've done it! Huzzah!</p><p>Here's your reward. But calm down a bit. You know that the enemy will be up in our beeswax again soon enough. The headaches never abate for long! </p><p>Are you tired? Alas, the only way to get any rest is to go home to mommy, head back to Nezebgrad, to Novograd, or board a ship. We've got a war going on here!</p></html>