<html>After using the alchemic mortar, place the following ingredients inside: herbs with the required properties and auxiliary substances that you can buy from me. <br/>The properties of the ingredients used must form a harmonious combination. If you can ensure that, you'll get a potion whose effect depends directly on how well-matched the properties are. Yet the brewing process can result in a failure. You need to be ready for that and not lose hope. <br/>By increasing your skill level, you'll gain access to new, more sophisticated and powerful formulas. Try making exactly these potions: the more sophisticated the formula, the greater the increase in your skill. However, making potions of levels surpassed long ago won't help your development. Your skill level depends on your character level as well: you can't become a high-class master if you stop developing. </html>