<html>Do you want to learn how to make relics? Of course you do, that's the ultimate feat in our craft! <br/>Now that you've reached those heights, I can share this knowledge with you. <br/>Relics differ from ordinary items in that they have a high content of astral energy. First of all, you'll need a blueprint for the item you want to make. You can get blueprints yourself on islands, or you can simply buy what you need from other astral conquerors. You can use blueprints to make both relics and upgrading items. <br/>Additionally, you'll need certain materials. <br/>First of all, it's metal and coal. You should be able to get these easily. <br/>Second, it's monograms. Not the ordinary stuff but the kind found on astral islands. You can get it yourself or buy it from other heroes.<br/>Third, it's traceries. These are very delicate components. They become completely useless for you once anyone else has laid their hands on them. That's why you'll have to obtain them on astral islands by yourself.<br/>And here's the last thing you need to know. The created relic is... so to say, empty. It won't be bound to you, unlike those found on the islands, and you won't be able to use it. The relic needs to be activated first. For that, you'll need relic fragments. You may have guessed that you'll have to go to the islands to get them as well. Depending on the quality of your work, you will need more or fewer relic fragments to activate a relic. </html>