<html><p>Several years ago we sent our best scouts to search for our homeland, a beautiful allod named Isa that my people were forced to leave. Getting home is our main objective. Ton the Windblower's expedition was thought to be extremely promising, but now we've received this heartbreaking news!</p><p>Well, let's not get dejected. Some of the scouts have not yet reported back. If they can't find our promised land either, well, we can always send more. The Astral is large and has plenty of elbow room.</p><p>By the way, we're running low on asters. These flowers are delicate, and we don't trust the Council's rough hands with gathering them. Will you take the job?</p><p>Asters are a kind of flower that are very useful in Astral journeys. Don't even bother asking us what's so special about them. It's a great Gibberling secret. Please go to Amberwood in the east and pick five of them for us.</p></html>