<html><p>So, the journals have been collected. I will read you a passage from one of them. It should hopefully give you the answer.</p><p>"When hunting season opens, it is time for the deer to become lizards. When the fishing boats set sail, it is time for the fish to become seashells. When glaciers approach, it is time for the elephants to become mammoths.</p><p>You must change the part of yourself that is known to the enemy. What remains will be a new being that is not recognized by your foes."</p><p>I can sense that you're still confused. Alright, I have one more hint for you. This should make it clear who we are.</p></html>