<html><p>The only source of knowledge is experience! If you hadn't noticed it's pretty cold out here, but that doesn't mean you can sit around and do nothing. You've got to get out there, do stuff, and learn or else you'll just freeze to death. Lucky for you, I've got some work to help you stay occupied. If you complete all of my assignments I promise that you'll be generously rewarded.</p></html>