<html><p>We Orcs are viewed by others as a barbaric race, capable only of fistfights. This is far from the truth, for we can be skilled in magic as well! The Orcish race has huge potential. Right now we can only master nature magic, but long, long ago our tribe produced its own Great Mage. He held together our allod as well as the Xadaganian mages.</p><p>We call him the Legendary Orc. Unfortunately, all traces of him have vanished into history but we, his followers, will continue to search for his fate until the end of our days! When I say "we" I mean the shamans and all of our loyal friends.</p><p>We have some clues, one of which is you. Yes, you! Our totem summons a hostile spirit to fight any newcomers to our territory. However, according to the legend, if the spirits detect someone of value many of them will appear to prove the newcomer's worth. That means our hopes lie with you now.</p><p>Wait, don't go. We have to communicate with the friendly spirits now so that they might guide you. We have to summon them using an ancient Blood Ritual. Don't worry, it's not your blood we need. Bring me the blood of spiders so that we may begin.</p></html>