<html><p>Great Nezeb, Skrakan, and even Tensess! The wounded keep arriving and arriving. The Servants of the Light are capable of many things... but not quite miracles.</p><p>These wounds inflicted by the demons are horrific. Dark energy spreads throughout the wounded very quickly, and sometimes the only option is to amputate the infected part. Half of those who become injured end up disabled!</p><p>There is one remedy. If we cauterize the wounds with powerful flames the infections can be stopped from spreading. Such flames can be found on the fire elementals to the west. Verkhovin is too busy to send out soldiers to collect them for us, but perhaps you can help?</p></html>