<html><p>I've been sent a very odd message. I'm sure you know all about this, but recently the Demon Hunters in Dragon Ring were able to enter into a treaty with Soliskar. Together they're fighting the remaining demons. That's pretty fantastic, right? But here's where it gets really interesting...</p><p>Soliskar, the leader of all the dragons, has used the Demon Hunters to send us a message. She would like to temporarily ally with us in this fight against the demons, but we must first prove ourselves first.</p><p>There's a dragon with a bounty on his head on this very allod. You see, this dragon and his clan have allied with the demons. Soliskar does not approve of this and so she's asked for his execution!</p><p>She says that if we bring her his fang, she'll side with us against the demons until we retake Yazes Shard! We need that tooth! Go to the Blackened Shore and kill Kuzurgar the Traitor!</p></html>