The Inspiration Bar is located in the right part of the crafting interface. If you manage to craft an item using 2, 3, or 4 purple item parts your inspiration will increase for that design. With Level 1 Inspiration, you will be able to change one of the parts to a purple one. Level 2 Inspiration change up to 2 parts to purple ones. Inspiration points are counted separately for each design until you have made 5 different items using other designs, at which point you'll lose the accumulated inspiration points.