<html>I have never been to Hikut Isle, but I know that it floats near the Holy Land. It's not surprising that both the League and the Empire fought for this allod in an attempt to use it as a base camp and fortify their positions.<br/>Eventually, the Empire won the battle and seized the allod. But it's here that the story really gets interesting. You see, just a few weeks later the Xadaganian garrison defending the allod betrayed the Empire!<br/>Obviously there were cultists were among the soldiers. Maybe it happened because a giant demonic worm entrenched itself in the middle of the allod… They say those creatures can corrupt people's minds.<br/>Izbor Yavorsky himself recently asked me to look for heroes willing to help the League. At the moment our army cannot afford to send an expedition to the allod, but someone has to clear it of demons in the name of the League! I'm entitled to assign you with this task. Are you in?</html>