<html><p>You feel a wave of hatred and discontent. You see a hillside, a path winding up, hordes of undead and draconids are forcing the demons back. The demons are retreating, they are falling under a torrent of blows raining on them all around... The attack is repelled! And again! And again! </p><p>You feel despair overcoming you. It is impossible to fight your way through countless enemy ranks, pressing from all sides.</p><p> Astral... The beautiful, bewitching Astral is calling to you. The demons want more than anything to go home, they see no reason to continue these senseless attacks... But their creator's command will not allow them to return until their mission is completed.</p></html>