<html><p>In the League, only Elves learn necromantic magic. The Kanians and Gibberlings are too afraid of the power, can you believe it? Fools!</p><p>I myself have devoted considerable time to study of those arts, in this life and my past. They are very powerful, and in my humble opinion the League would have won long ago if more of their citizens practiced them.</p><p>Because of this, I know that whenever those Elven necromancers appear, they must be killed as quickly as possible! The sooner they're out of the way, the sooner the League troops will be defeated.</p><p>At the moment there is an Elven necromancer on the allod. Our agents have learned that his name is Louis de Desirae, and that he is quite powerful. It will not be easy to defeat him, but it would give our troops a great advantage. Perhaps you can gather some friends to help you defeat this despicable Elf.</p></html>