<html><p>I have another task for you. Strewn around these ruins are our notes. They contain information about our past, our current plans, and our hopes for the future.</p><p>Unfortunately, many of them were stolen during the demons' assaults. Our common enemy wants to know our plans so that they may defeat us.</p><p>The loss of these notes has been a serious blow. Without them we will have to revise our plans and rewrite them from scratch.</p><p>If you can return them to us in the near future, then we may still be able to salvage the situation. We know that the cultists possess most of the pages now. Kill them and pry the notes from their dead hands, then return them to me.</p></html>