<html><p>Now that the problem with Yasker is solved, we can focus on other affairs.</p><p>As you know, the goal of our Kirah operations is meteorite ore. We have captured a part of the Blazing Mine and started the extraction, but a large segment is still under control of our enemies. So the League and the Empire are now fighting underground. Until the mine is ours, I can't even think about truce.</p><p>You can change everything. Help us to clean up the mine from the Imperial soldiers and miners!</p></html>