<html><p>The portal will now send you to another Astral allod - Forlorn Isle.</p><p>In the middle of it you will see an ancient pyramid. It was built over the place where the Great Dragon Hunter of the June found his eternal rest.</p><p>The restless spirit of the Hunter is still wandering around the tomb. It's difficult to explain, but the most important thing for us is that the spirit can give you a special token, the Charm of Astral Silver.</p><p>I see you want to know how the charm is related to the Astral and to the powers of the Great Martyrs. And maybe you are curious about the fact that this thousand years old charm will help you defeat the demon created in the future?</p><p>One day you will know the answers. But it won't happen before you get the charm.</p></html>