There are a lot! Firstly, Best Friends can go enter Dungeons together, even if they significantly differ in levels. Secondly, they can give each other a hand in Astral quests. Thirdly, one may teleport to their Best Friend from the farthest edges of Sarnaut. And finally, Best Friends can lend each other the most precious things: their mounts and astral ships. So, how deeply do you trust each other?