<html><p>There's a certain mystery that the Keeper of Secrets has been trying to solve for a while now. Unfortunately, he doesn't have enough evidence. However, I believe that document may be just what he's been looking for.</p><p>You see, in six hundred forty-six of the New Era a Great Mage named Danas uncovered the secret allod of Umoira. There he helped Skrakan defeat a great demon. We know this information from ancient documents that the City Council retrieved from the Kanian government.</p><p>Unfortunately, those are all the details we have. Danas was very solitary, and most of his secrets were only recorded in his personal diary. This document was considered lost for many years, but a short while ago a few pages of it were found.</p><p>Shortly afterwards the pages were locked in separate chests for safekeeping. But as luck may have it, in a matter of days they were lost when the ship that was carrying them was destroyed.</p><p>This page is from that fabled diary! With this, our government will be able to solve some pretty ancient riddles. For your help, you will be well rewarded!</p></html>