<html><p>Do you know that the ancient June were the greatest masters of gem cutting?</p><p>Just so you know - they could cut a full body armor out of a huge diamond! A soldier in such armor was nearly invulnerable.</p><p>Good news is that our masters managed to reproduce some of June works! As you know, a person could only wear a single magic earring earlier, the second caused strong magical resonance, so they suppressed the powers of each other. But the secrets of June helped our jewelers to find a way to safely equip the second earring! Isn't it great?</p><p>Jewelers' knowledge is kept in the manuscripts that can be found in the Strongboxes sold from the Item Shop. If you manage to find the Expert Jeweler's Manuscript, bring it to me, and I'll teach you how to equip a second earring of the rare quality!</p><p>I can also trade ten Expert Jeweler's Manuscripts for a Artisan Jeweler's Manuscript.</p></html>