<html><p>Another traveler wanting to use the portal I'm guessing? Unfortunately we have a pest keeping it locked down, so I'm afraid you can't use it until things are cleaned up here.</p><p>If you'd like you can take this key and go deal with it yourself. It'd help me out a lot. You'd also get to use the portal of course. You know the drill - help it feed on souls until it thinks it's invincible, then challenge it to a battle and burst its little bubble by defeating it. Then it'll leave us in peace!</p></html>