<html><p>So, shall we continue hunting cowards and traitors? Good. A whole bunch of deserters have set up camp in the ancient Jakala Ruins.</p><p>And get this - renegades from both the Empire and the League camp there side by side. Birds of a feather, huh! And to think how much money was spent equipping both. For what? So they could fight each other - not run off into the woods, room together, and lead other soldiers astray too!</p><p>We've been given an order to raid their camp and show them what a good traitor is. You guessed it - a dead one. Make sure to kill as many defectors as possible from both sides.</p></html>