<html><p>Welcome to the Astral Academy! This is where new adventurers learn about the Astral, while experienced pilots patch up their ships between expeditions.</p><p>Do you want to try your luck in the Astral? Good for you. I must warn you, though, that it isn't a good place to visit if you lack experience in battle. You should prove your worthiness on land first!</p><p>Still, if you feel you're ready the compete with the veteran Astral travelers, you are more than welcome here!</p></html>