<html><p>This strange chain is pulsing with magic. It looks like a truly sinister artifact, but you cannot determine what it was used for.</p><p>You'd better take it to Yasker and tell him what's happened here! He must know of the existence of the strange creature that called itself Sarn, and its threats to all of Sarnaut! Could it truly have been controlling the cultists and the demons all along?</p></html>