The bottom of an empty chest contains a greeting card:
"Dear hero! Your path was difficult and great are your accomplishments. Your glory will not fade for centuries! Your deeds are forever recorded into the history of Sarnaut, and for this anniversary we would like to present you with a gift, a rare glyph. You can select a glyph from the Holiday Committee Official, Zinaida Krichalkina.
We congratulate you on this celebration and wish you all the best!"