<html><p>Hail to the Chosen One on their way to the Revelation! Remember - fighting is not always the solution. If we cannot dominate foes by force then outsmarting them is the preferred option.</p><p>Up ahead you will come across some terrible ogres. When Ath-Zak was still recovering from his struggle with the wolf he had no strength to fight the savages. Instead, he lay on his belly and carefully crawled past the ogres like a snake.</p><p>Show me that you can outdo the beasts as Ath-Zak once did. You'll eventually meet my comrade along the road. Speak to the Spirit of Bravery once you have passed this test!</p></html>