<html>Tep grabbed your boys by the neck and used them as cleaning rags, didn't he? Oh, this should be good! Did you expect to find a skinny old man, cuff him and take him to the capital for a fair trial? Hello! This is Tep! To him, Sparks are a snack and genocide is entertainment on boring nights! All we did so far only caused him some inconvenience - nothing more!<br/>Now don't start panicking. He can be defeated, or I wouldn't be talking to you now. You know why he let you go? He wants to play cat-and-mouse with you. Tep doesn't even think the Resistance poses any threat to him. His presumption will ruin him... If yours doesn't kill you first, of course.</html>