<html><p>All of these people are sitting here in paradise without a care for anything but themselves. Oh, the living are so selfish! This place should be a paradise for everything inside, but I feel like I'm the only one who cares about this. Or perhaps not the only one? Maybe you're concerned about this too?</p><p>You see, I'm worried about this tiny tree growing in the center of the dome. Yes, it is a Great Tree, but it's still just a baby. And how do you think it feels, growing in a thin layer of imported soil, surrounded by sand and salt? Not much of a paradise if you ask me!</p><p>Here's what I'm thinking of doing - we could release some worms into the soil around its roots. They might loosen up the ground and make it easier for the baby to grow. Will you help me out? Here's the box of worms you need. I'd help you out myself, but I've only got one box. I can't figure out where I put the second one...</p></html>