<html><p>Wow, those are some beautiful eggs - perfectly shaped and free of any scratches! Alright, take this Shipbuilder's Certificate. You can use it to speed up the construction of your ship whenever you want to.</p><p>So, you still want to know why we want these, eh? Fine, I'll tell you. Soliskar has agreed to let us raise our own whelps. Then they'll become our loyal companions and help us hunt the demons! Isn't that great? Thanks for making this possible.</p></html>