<html><p>The cultists' ritual was disrupted! It turns out that their summoned demon was not quite as dangerous as one might have expected. Perhaps it's because it was only recently summoned.</p><p>Still, a demon is a demon and its appearance hints at darker things to come. The demon's heart must be brought to Esther de Desirae. It's about time for her to do something useful around here!</p></html>