<html><p>Any war is chaos. Unrest, confusion, discord, general distrust...</p><p>But chaos is much more than simply destruction. Chaos is the foundation of all things. If not for chaos, there would be no development, and the world would remain forever still. Order can tame chaos, and then at the converge of the two forces emerges a third, whose name is life.</p><p>You want to live? Do you want your friends, your brothers and sisters in arms, your entire peoples to live? Then tame chaos, which is carried by the Master's enemies into this world. And remember - only order can defeat chaos!</p></html>