<html><p>I have another request for you. A third cousin of ours by the name of Ophelia is busy collecting plants from the forest. She wants to start promoting their use in city gardens. But before she can do that she needs to have some examples to showcase.</p><p>You should be able to find her to the northeast near the waterfall. Collect a good number of lilies of the valley and sorrel and bring them to Ophelia. I'm sure she'll be very grateful!</p></html>