<html><p>When you find a deposit of ore you can use a pick to help you gather it. The quality and quantity of what you find depends on your skill level and where you are.</p><p>Remember that once you mine a deposit, it won't regenerate for a long time. Your best bet is to move on to other locations and look for new deposits. After you mine it, the ore that you've gathered can be used by blacksmiths to make armor and weapons.</p><p>Every time you successfully gather more ore, your skill in mining will increase. Eventually you will be able to find and gather more advanced types of ore. One more thing - you won't be able to increase your mining skill past a certain point until you've raised your overall level as well.</p></html>