<html><p>Light help us! The seers will be landing! Why didn't anyone warn me?! Damn it, think about how much better things would be without these lazy soldiers! I can't do anything with these soldiers!</p><p>Get to the shore right away. The Empire may have already killed them to prevent us from refuting their lies, but we have no way of knowing without any communication going on down here. Greet the little ones when they land and make sure they're alright.</p></html>