<html><p>Now, onward to the Palace Square! </p><p>Soon the warriors of Sarn will take it by siege. Gol'iath is coming from the west, and woe unto them who stand in his way. Here, in the east, we need to help Gromov. He'd be glad to attack right now, but he knows that the undead would just pour right in behind him.</p><p>To ensure that no one interferes with our commander's ability to crush the defenders of the Palace Square into smithereens, we'll need to clear the way.</p><p>You've already probably seen enough of the undead for a while. I myself don't quite understand where they come from, or how there got to be so many. Well, I must admit I have my guesses... We'll talk about all that some other time.</p><p>Annihilate the undead around the Wretched Reach and in the meantime we'll start preparing to assault the Palace Square.</p></html>