<html><p>I am Amadeus and I've been created to work on this Galleon. I possess keen intuition and am fully conversational. Vocabulary - ten thousand words. Emotions deactivated. For detailed instructions see my developer - the Great Mage Gorluxor.</p><p>Password required to stop beam apparatus. You have stated the wrong password. You have one attempt left. If you state the wrong password again, the room will be blocked off and guards will be called.</p></html>