<html>Astral reflections occur only in the deepest layers of the Astral. On the outside, they look like real and familiar locations, but their content differs greatly from what you would expect. For example, a castle where some knight used to live will be occupied by undead or werewolves in its reflection. Where a river used to run, lava or corrosive acid may flow. Enemies may not appear as what they seem...
As I understand, astral reflections are images of the future, past or present that reveal a possible outcome of an event. Exploring these reflections is very dangerous, since you can never know what you will deal with, but the reward upon a victory may be significant!</html>