<html>Listen to me, outlander. I lived and did great things, and died long, long time ago. I cleansed the jungle so People could have place to live. I killed a monstrous octopus so that People could go fishing. I invented a chopper, a rope, a flint to make fire in the fireplace and drums for dancing. I died and slept in peace, and People burned early fruits and sweet meat in memory of Arikee.<br/>Then People became foolish. A brother ripped a brother, and a wing went to war against another wing, and People became two tribes. The path to my grave grew over, old songs were forgotten, everything was for the war, for the victory. And I cried in my grave. Then, big darkness came from the outside, killed both tribes. I was old, wise and dead, I knew the outcome. Unworthy descendants did not know and they continued their war, although they all were dead for a long time. And then a stupid shaman came here, summoned my spirit and asked me to help the Steel Claw in the war against the White Wing! I did not know if I should laugh or weep! I punished that fool and scattered his brains all over the forest.<br/>So you outlander are fighting a big rotting god who lives beyond the world and want to help that old fool? Well, I can forgive the shaman if you complete my task.<br/>First, find a sacred ritual gourd. They used to carry sweet wine, then they forgot about it, and it was stolen by monkeys. Take the sacred gourd from monkeys. And punish filthy animals, teach them never mess on my grave again!</html>