<html><p>So that's the truth of the matter... Thank you for getting to the bottom of everything and saving our colony. If Alexander's plan had succeeded, he would've sent us to our deaths battling the pirates before blasting us into the Astral. That bastard!</p><p>Our colony will eventually recover from the damage. Once everything's back to normal, you should come visit us again! We'll hold a great celebration in your honor! Thank you so much for helping us!</p></html>