<html><p>Wait! The forestfolk need you. You look like a strong warrior and we need help from your kind. The voices of the forestfolk always fall on deaf ears... All these Free Traders do is swear and count their gold. But our people our vanishing! Someone must care.</p><p>Our chief sent me to this bazaar to find allies. We hoped that many brave souls would pass through here, with hearts full of compassion for the children of nature.</p><p>Here, please take this letter. This scroll is covered with the ancient writings of my people. You will find our settlement to the east of Icemirror Lake, by the roaring falls. Show our leader this letter and tell him that I sent you. Then he will tell you what you can do to save us!</p></html>