<html>Weaponsmiths are always in demand: we make swords and spiked clubs, bows and crossbows, and even magic wands. But before you get down to crafting weapons, you'll have to practice making kitchen knives and simple hammers. <br/>
Now, about the process itself. Use a mobile forge to learn the list of blueprints available and prepare the right components. You can buy coal for your work from me. Use a pick to extract ore that should then be cast in the molds you need. Parts will be harder to obtain. Rods, tips, bases, blades, braidings, additives, flux, granulations, enamels... All of that can be obtained by fighting enemies or bought from other heroes. <br/>
The forging process is simple: you create five parts, check their quality, keep the good ones and reforge the rest. You can only reforge each part twice, and you work on at least two parts at a time. <br/>
If all parts are of equal quality, you'll get an item of that same quality. If the quality is uncommon, you'll even get two items. If not, you'll get the item anyway, but it won't be as good as it could be. <br/>
You'll gain experience for each item you make. When you've gained enough experience, your skill level will increase and new blueprints will be available to you. The maximum available level of weaponsmithing equals your character level. <br/>
Keep in mind that, as your skill level increases, you only gain access to the simplest blueprints that allow making items for personal use. But there are other, more sophisticated and expensive blueprints that you'll have to buy or obtain by yourself. They will allow you to craft items for sale to other heroes, higher-level items or even relics. <br/>
By the way, if you ever need lower-level components, you can use retroform that you can buy from me as well. Don't worry, a single vial will last for a while. Keep in mind, though, that retroform affects neither ore nor the goods made from it. </html>