<html><p>It really is an amazing story... We already knew about the destruction of Clement's Tower, but now the identity of the culprit has been revealed as well.</p><p>I'm not surprised, for rebellions have been flaring all across Kania. Even Oreshek Fortress, located right here in Lightwood, has recently been captured. Someone is pulling at the strings of a giant cobweb that entangles all of Kania! I wish I could reach the spider that's controlling it...</p><p>And I hear you've solved the mysteries of some ancient June technology? At least there's some good news in the midst of all these troubles! These Meteorite... or, what did you call it? These Adventurer's Stones will revolutionize travel in Kania!</p><p>All of Clement's stones will be distributed to the people immediately, and many mages are now frantically searching for more! They've even started trying to imbue the ancient magic into new Stones to create more!</p><p>If you want to continue to serve your country you can go visit the Novograd Construction Council. Their tasks might be a bit more mundane than your previous adventures, but they're always in need of dependable people. Building a new capital is no Gibberling sized task!</p></html>