<html>Do you even know what this is? I don't believe my eyes! This is an ancient relic which was lost with the arrival of the heretical false gods! Like a fragile flower sprouting on withered soil, a new hope sprouts for the Tekyan people!<br/>Know that this "medallion," as you called it in your ignorance, is actually the Forest Yantra - an ancient symbol of harmony with nature! The Tekyans of ages past meditated on its intricate patterns to attain awareness of their unity with roots and branches. They strolled through the woods immersed in wise and righteous thoughts, without fear of getting lost. When the "immortals" came, monkeys stole this relic from our sanctum. Evidently, wild animals were more deserving of keeping it than we were! But now the relic has been returned! Oh, what blessing! Oh, what fortune!</html>