<html><p>Next on the list is flowers. I'll give you three red roses to hand out to the lovely women of our nation. Typical yes, but always a favorite. Women have always found flowers to be a welcome gift.</p><p>Why? To be honest, I don't know. I think the point is that the flowers are beautiful and by giving them to a woman we are telling her that she is just as beautiful as the flower.</p><p>In any case, they're in season and bursting with life, so go out there and hand them out while they're still pretty. Tell me when you're done so I know that the women have been made that much happier.</p></html>