Sabantuy is a traditional orcish holiday. Sabantuy originates from the time when the world was still whole and the orcish race led a nomadic life in the vast steppes. All the orcish tribes would gather for a celebration. Mighty fighters would compete in crushing rocks with their bare hands, drinking up barrels of beer on a wager, and hammering each other on the head until only the toughest orc with the strongest forehead would remain on his feet. The winner would earn a war club as a reward, as well as the respect of the tribe. A lot has changed since. The orcs have become esteemed citizens of the Empire, but the tradition of celebrating Sabantuy remains. And when an orc visits an artisan during the celebration, he can become the lucky owner of valuable gifts and souvenirs.