<html><p>I have a new task for you. I want you to visit the contraband trader - I'd be willing to bet that the cultists are already lying in wait for you there. But the cultists are known for their fanaticism... even if they can be taken prisoner, they won't say a word! They say that they'd rather die.</p><p>So here's what I propose... I want you to take this magic mark and place it on the leader of the bunch. But then you'll have to die - and make it look convincing! After your resurrection, return to the church for new instructions.</p><p>That magic mark will help us follow the cultists and stake out their lair. Here, take this dagger with you for added credibility - the cultists won't suspect a thing.</p></html>