<html><p>Our intelligence agency has been plagued by misfortune. Just a few days ago more of our agents disappeared. They're called the Audacious Family.</p><p>A cousin of our grandmother's neighbor's sister recently saw them in Siveria. She said the Audacious Family was visiting their relatives in Siveria for a few days but then they just vanished without a trace. They might have been kidnapped by the enemy or eaten by a local beast...</p><p>Like all the other Gibberling reconnaissance agents, the Audacious Family was involved in the search for our lost homeland. That's why we desperately need to know what they found on their last mission.</p><p>You've been such a great help in the past, so we were hoping you'd be willing to help again. We need you to find out what happened to them. You should start in Gravestein. It's a small Gibberling settlement in Siveria. Talk to the Eye Family when you get there. They're the mothers of the Audacious Family.</p></html>