<html><p>Wait a moment! Hmm, you haven't passed a Consecration Ritual. This is unacceptable!</p><p>Every Kanian man or woman, regardless of their beliefs, must pass the Consecration Ritual and accept Light into their hearts. It is an edict of Voisvet himself! Even if you choose the path of a mage and study elemental magic, you must do it!</p><p>The Church of Light awaits you! Go there immediately and do everything prescribed to you by the church's canons. Believe me, this will be better for everyone, especially for you.</p><p>The ritual is quite simple. First of all, you must talk to the first priest of the Church of Light and confess your sins.</p><p>Secondly, you must take communion by touching the pedestal with the Holy Testaments of Tensess.</p><p>Thirdly, a second priest must anoint you with holy oil.</p><p>After that, you must be baptized in holy water.</p><p>And lastly, you must accept the oath of the Church of Light. This will be done by a third priest of the Church of Light.</p><p>All clear? Go and don't come back until you pass the ritual. Understand that in the future you will have to fight the cunning Imperial soldiers and many merciless demons. How will you fare in these battles without accepting the Light into your heart?</p></html>