<html><p>Great. This should be enough gel for the ritual. Now all we need is to find a new body. As you know, nobody's about to give up their body willingly. That's why you need to take it from someone - preferably someone who's undeserving of sympathy.</p><p>You forget that I can read your mind. Remember - the League and the Empire must become allies. Your current proposal is not an option.</p></html>