<html><p>I'm glad you're taking interest in leatherworking. Frankly, I'm one of the only master leatherworkers and there's more work coming in than I can handle.</p><p>For your first task it'd be great if you could get started on the bridle our stable master has been requesting. I've been putting it off for quite some time and it's not fair to the stable master to wait so long. Just come back when you're done with the work and I'll be sure to inspect it for quality when it's complete.</p></html>