<html>How strange! The only bodies found next to the ship were those of Tep's cultists. One of them had a letter in his pocket that you found... It was signed by Charles de Doucer! This is so suspicious that perhaps the privacy of correspondence may be violated...<br/>Well, that's disappointing. The characters in the letter look familiar, but not the language. There's a plan in the letter, though: some carelessly sketched corridors and arrows. Looks like this is an escape plan indeed... But where from, exactly? This find should be shown to the rebels' leader.</html>