<html>Sh... They're not here? Quiet, they may hear us!<br/>Where are you from? I thought none of ours was alive! Those who didn't die in the crash were taken by those... things. Are you sure one of them isn't around? We need to be careful, or they may take us too!<br/>What? The Resistance? Holy moly, then why am I sitting here, afraid to stick my nose outside? Thank you! I'll hurry over to our guys.<br/>Wait, wait, I almost forgot. When they came, they took both the living and the dead, ripped everything of value off the ship, but failed to open the captain's safe. They're still hanging around trying to crack it, but nuts to them: it's made in the Empire! Don't know what's in there, but I'm sure it's not some trash. I've kept the key, take it. See you in the Refuge!</html>