<html>Traitorous anarchists are crafty and agile. I watch them. They are very careful bastards, twitching from slightest noise, flying like lightning. Wingless one cannot catch them up. Still, it's good to be quick, but it's better to be smart!<br/>Lianas grow in the jungle. Very durable lianas. No one among the People of the Wind can tear it. Wingless one is strong, you can pluck lianas. I will make durable net from lianas. Traitors entangle themselves in the net and will not escape. Then wingless one will take them to the city and have our chief punish them. The chief will be happy, thank outlander and reward me with the best hen to marry! Wingless one does not need a hen anyway, while I want to bring up chicks. </html>