<html>I was going to my bride, beloved Gia. Then a black flock of harpies swooped in! They hit me in my beak and my eye and took my bag. The bag contained a present, a beautiful necklace. I've made it for the wedding. It took me a long time to make it! I wanted to give the necklace to Gia and ask her to marry me.<br/>Dirty chickens are those harpies, they stole the bag and threw it atop the Giant's Claw. The bag opened, the necklace fell out and broke. Gems scattered everywhere. Hungry squawkers ate everything. Gems were beautiful and shiny. Squawkers swallowed all the gems! <br/>Poor, poor Torrick! Now I have nothing to give my bride. It would be better if I die...</html>