<html><p>I can only make light armor out the plates I have. Tough as they are, they are still far too fragile for a heavy breastplate. A few strong blows would be enough to crack them.</p><p>I need something stronger... Like the plates of a very mature gar. </p><p>I saw one like it in the depths of the Hissing Canyon. A horrible beast! I don't think you can kill him on your own. But if you're not alone... So gather your friends and go. Bring me its breastplate! My reward will be generous.</p></html>