<html><p>Osip is boycotting us? Well, I suppose that was to be expected. I would gladly give him a final death if he weren't such a key part of our plan.</p><p>I suppose we should negotiate the terms of his resurrection if he won't cooperate any longer. Are you surprised at such an easy victory? Well, fortunately for Osip we may soon achieve our goal and then this whole thing can end.</p><p>But I warn you, you'll have to work hard for Osip's resurrection to succeed. Think carefully if you're willing to go to such lengths for this ghost...</p></html>