<html>Greetings, pleased to meet you. I heard plenty about you... I was sent here by Charles de Doucer to help you find a passage. The girl briefed me on the situation - not in a particularly scientific way, but she got the gist of it nonetheless. The Crystal Palace is separated from the surrounding world by a barrier I've dubbed the "Paradox Viel." It is a wall made up of the impossible: the final stronghold of Tep, and also his demise, for it is a blatant violation of all existing laws of this world. Presently the force of the paradox helps the web to maintain the illusion, but if it is destroyed, this world will reject its creator with equal force. Do you realize what that means? We are but one step away from victory! But have no doubt - this step will be more difficult than all the others combined.<br/>We'll begin, as always, with research. Take this device - let's call it "reality meter." Take it to the Paradox Veil, take some measurements and, if you survive, bring it back.</html>