<html><p>Most people only care about the artifacts in Coba Plateau, but if you look harder you might notice a few other interesting things as well. However, you need to know how to look for details first!</p><p>For this reason I've hired some Prospectors to hide six magical stones around Coba Plateau. You need to find all of them to learn how to find the more obscure things around here. Then you can use those techniques to find tons of other things!</p><p>You can find the stones in the Meridian Outback, the Rusted Wasteland, the Giant's Table, the Midnight Shore, the Spectral Gorge, and the Southern Bank. Good luck!</p></html>