<body>
<p>A Radiant Strongbox can contain some of Sarnaut's most wondrous treasures.</p>
<p>This box will contain a Collector's Coin that can be used to buy valuable goods from the Goblin Banker. It will also reward most people with useful items that can help them throughout their adventures. However, the Radiant Strongbox can reward a chosen few with an extremely valuable item - a Free Traders' Reactor Plans or a Free Traders' Motor Plans!</p>
<p>Free Traders' Reactor Plans will grant you a legendary reactor for your Astral ship. Free Traders' Motor Plans will grant you a legendary motor for your Astral Ship.</p>
<p>There is a high chance that the Radiant Strongbox will contain a Free Traders' Cannon Plans, Mana Batteries, an Astral Servant, a Mechanic's Rune, a Barrel of Astral Emanations, a Coupon Book, a Builder's Rune, a Bundles of Astral Megaphones, a Cerulean Wolf Pattern, or a Light Chestnut Steed or Buckskin Runner Patterns.</p>
<p>There is a low chance that the Radiant Strongbox will contain a Free Traders' Shield Plans.</p>
<p>There is an extremely low chance that the Radiant Strongbox will contain a Free Traders' Motor Plans or a Free Traders' Reactor Plans.</p>
<p>Some of the items in this box may bind when picked up.</p>
<p>This item is consumed after use and can be traded to other players.</p>
</body>