<html><p>Thierry must be a prophet - he told me that you would come. I must confess, I'm glad to see you.</p><p>You know, we're in a terrible situation. Of course, we explained everything to our soldiers. They saw the tentacle you brought but they're still confused. The enemy is still terrible and unknown!</p><p>I want you to show them how it's done! Kill some demons and nail their tentacles to the pole to the northeast of our camp, along the road. It will cheer up our soldiers!</p></html>