<html><p>We've been getting a ton of new recruits lately. It seems like more pour in every day! And none of them have even semi-decent gear. I'm not sure what they're expecting. That the jungle will be full of bunnies and butterflies?</p><p>The army has made it my job to gear out every single new recruit. And to provide other supplies as well, of course! I Apart from the heap of plate armor, I have an urgent order for locks to secure the prisons.</p><p>Hey, do you think you could help me out a bit? Bring me some locks  - I don't care if you make them yourself or buy them off another skilled blacksmith. Just help me finish this order!</p></html>