<html>A stream of ice afflicts the target with the Ice Flow effect, reducing the target's movement speed by 15% per stack, and mount speed by 10% per each stack. The effect can reach five stacks, lasts two seconds and is renewed every second while Beam of Ice is active.<br/>Beam of Ice deals damage every second equal to 1% of the hit points of the Overlord's Aegis. This damage grows by 1% of the hit points of the Overlord's Aegis per each stack of the Freeze effect on the target. <br/>Range 40 meters, maximum duration 20 seconds. Requires 5 charges.</html>