<html><p>I've placed the bet and now it's time for our pet to enter the arena. Yeah, it was that easy. These Free Traders don't have many regulations when it comes to making profit.</p><p>I'm positive that our gar will tear that mantis to shreds! Watch the Elf's face carefully - it will soon be full of rage and dismay! As soon as we win I'll put the pressure on Etienne and then tell you what I've learned.</p></html>