<html><p>Incoming! Demons! All hands on deck!</p><p>Why are you just standing there? Run to the artillery before your ship is turned to a pile of scrap metal!</p><p>Oh, I forgot you're new to the Astral. In short, the artillery are those big thingies on both sides of the front of the ship. They're even marked as such - "Artillery." So run on over to them, wait for a demon to appear in your sights and let 'em rip!</p></html>