<html><p>What's this giant thing stuck in the snow? It glows eerily, as if enchanted by magic, and it gives off an otherworldly chill.</p><p>Whatever this is, it's clear that someone very powerful created it. Perhaps they made it to mark something useful that they had hidden in these forsaken peaks. You should probably dig around in the snow beneath it to see if you can find a treasure!</p></html>