<body>
<p><br>This Strongbox may contain Overlord's Aegis - a unique vehicle designed for mounted combat! In addition, it contains scrolls that enhance abilities of your mounts.</br></p>
<p><br>Expert Goblin at the Item Shop Headquarters will trade scrolls for the actual items..</br></p>
<p>This item can be used by characters of any level.</p>
<p>Hurry, this is a time-limited offer!</p>
<p><tip_grey><br>Stored in your bag.</br>
<br>Consumable.</br></tip_grey><tip_golden><br>Goods from the Item Shop.</br></tip_golden></p>
</body>