<html>Take a look around. What you see before you is Tequatl - the only settlement of our ancient nation. Its beauty rivals that of mandarin flowers in spring, though it cannot compare with the beauty of a city on the ruins of which it was built and whose name it bears.<br/>Tekuatl was the city of the Ancients. They were all-knowing, all-powerful and wielded great magic. The Ancients knew how to make rock come alive. They were masters of the heavens and the earth. Our small nation was like a younger sibling to them, and we lived our lives without worry. Only vague legends remain of those wonderful times.<br/>The Ancients had a sworn enemy. A monster from the Void which cannot be described: even the words are scared of him and fall to silence. Who he was and where he came from is beyond our grasp. The Enemy was so powerful that all of the Ancients' wisdom and magic wasn't enough to protect them. Before they perished, in their dying moments the Ancients made sure to save us, their children and heirs. We have built our own Tequatl on the ruins of the great Tequatl of the Ancients. Thus began a new era for my people - an era of darkness and solitude. We dug roots and hunted mice, learned to build fires and sew simple rough garments for wear. Long were those days, and filled with sorrow. So thunderous was the Tekyans' cry of despair that the world split into two!<br/>But everything changed when They came. The true gods appeared to our people. They have built their palace on the mountain and settled there. They taught our people to build houses, sew beautiful clothing from soft fabrics, and cook delicious food. And all they asked in return was our devotion. The gods are powerful, righteous and kind. And if you prove your faith, you too may experience their favor!</html>