<html><p>This unusual crystal emits a strange magical force. If it was cut in the correct way and connected to a power supply, it could probably make the tools of one of your ship's goblins super powerful! If anyone can use this crystal, it's the hangar overseer. Maybe you should visit him?</p><p>Note that you will need some extra parts to make the device compatible with the third layer of the Astral. You can craft them yourself, buy them from other alchemists, blacksmiths, tailors and leatherworkers, or find them on the Auction House.</p></html>