<html><p>Greetings!</p><p> Not so long ago, a breakthrough discovery has opened up a pathway to a distant, unexplored Astral. This Astral lacks the familiar allods, shows no reflections of heroic adventures, and there are no clear routes of travel.</p><p>Instead it is full of bizarre phenomena, anomalies, and strange creatures that have never been encountered in the nearer layers of the Astral. Who knows what kind of danger lurks there?</p><p>Demon Hunters consider it their duty to destroy any threat that might be hiding there, and they will use everything at their disposal in the pursuit of this goal.</p><p>During your travels in this distant astral, you might meet powerful demons. Having defeated a demon, you'll be able to use an Astral trap to capture its body's Astral essence. You will also find unstable anomalies, either just-forming or in the process of disintegrating, and these can be captured as well.</p><p>Bring me any anomalous emanations you've collected in the far Astral and you will be able to trade them for rare items or special equipment to be used against the demons.</p></html>