<html><p>It seems my initial assumptions were right. The steles on the Dark Shards are military objects that are activated by the ancient June artifact. The stele on the eastern side boosts your power, while the stele on the western side drains power from your enemies. Both are quite useful in battle!</p><p>This is valuable information. The Aviaks are planning an attack on the Dark Shards, so the magical properties of the steles will surely come in handy when we start to drive the enemy off our allod!</p></html>