<html><p>Who are you? What company? I don't remember you.</p><p>However, that's not surprising. We have many recruits here. Everyone wants to achieve glory, but it must be well deserved!</p><p>What have you done today for our victory? Why are you silent? The enemy is watching! The Empire won't retreat from Kirah peacefully!</p><p>Kill at least twenty Imperial Soldiers - it will bring you the respect of the Expeditionary Corps.</p></html>