<html><p>Patience is the key to success. I hope that this is something you have already learned. No, I can see that you are still interested in battle. You long to strike the enemy with your weapons, and you believe my advice to be insignificant.</p><p>If you heed my advice, your skill in battle will increase as well. It's useful in many situations, you see. Your next step is to use your appreciation and humility to master a third skill - patience.</p><p>Before you battle a truly formidable foe, you must remove all distractions and plan your actions carefully. After they are removed, you will be able to clear your thoughts and concentrate only on the task at hand. You must be patient and avoid facing great trials while you are unprepared.</p><p>Go out and kill any lesser evils that you find. Return to me when you are done, and perhaps then you will be able to battle the greater evils that inhabit this allod.</p></html>