<html><p>Verkhovin ordered the eastern coast of this allod to be scouted by Astral ship. As you know, that mission already failed. He asked me if I could complete the mission on foot because I was part of the ship's crew, but there's no way I'd get past those cultists!</p><p>The only weapon I'm good with is a cannon, you know. I'm not a scout! But you... you look pretty capable. Maybe you could take this mission on yourself? I'm sure you'd succeed. And this mission needs to be a success. Verkhovin said it was very important. It better be important if my ship was sacrificed for it!</p><p>So what do you say? Help me out? Just go north along the coast as far as you can go and tell me what you see.</p></html>