<html>Interesting... So, the cultists managed to break through the magic barrier and enter the cave. They met an Ancient Guardian there who killed most of them with a deadly magic, "the spell of the Ancient Ones" - that is how the cultists refer to Junes.<br/>So this Ancient Guard is a June creation... But I have never heard that golems, the only June creations that survived to this day, were capable of using magic. I suspect that you will meet something unknown in Cave of Tka-Rik.</html>