	<html>Well, how do you feel? No longer dizzy? Great! Since you are all right, then help me revive the other survivors. The impact was so strong that the boarding crew from the upper deck was cast everywhere along the shore. I pray to Tensess that our guys are all right.<br/>Go, find survivors, revive them and send them here. I'll tend to their wounds. And question those who are conscious. Perhaps they saw something that may explain the cause of the shipwreck.</html>