<html><p>Cards! There are all sorts of fine words and wishes to be said to those who defend the Empire. Rysina herself approved of the raw emotion that can be displayed in a card!</p><p>Here - hand some out and let the men know that you care about their efforts. Seeing that someone respects your work provides great motivation, you know. This will also earn you a good reputation with the Spring Committee.</p></html>