<html>Is the dragon destroyed? Hehe. I wonder how the horde of draconids will get on without their Fiery Father? Although, there's still Soliskar the Wise and Agrus the Callous... No big deal. They're not interfering now. I hope that they can learn their lesson well and not try to cross me. And if they should once again start meddling where they don't belong... What's one more dead dragon, right?</html>