<html><p>Voisvet Belov! Also known as Voisvet Ironfist, the Hero of the Great Astral Campaign, the High Knight of the Church of Light, and the head of the Kanian Council of Governors. The man is truly a legend!</p><p>It's a pity he's not in Novograd right now. He left for the Holy Land to fight for Tensess Temple. What does that mean? It means that he will soon earn another title - the Liberator of the Holy Land!</p></html>