<html><p>This is an important question.</p><p>When the Great Tensess who perished during the demon invasion was in Tep's Pyramid, he had enough strength to withstand the ancient evil. Sacred Tensess was victorious, and from him we all received a great gift - the ability to resurrect. </p><p>But Tep left us with a curse, and for a long time it spoiled our lives! Unable to defile the innately pure Spark, the vile curse could only ruin some of the items in the equipment of the fallen hero. Fortunately, now we have found a way to fight this onslaught, and now your equipment is well protected from the curse. Trophies that you receive after defeating the enemy may still be found cursed. If that happens, buy a special Purifying Scrolls in the Item Shop and rid the object of the Curse.</p><p>You should discuss all this with Lovewise Catfish, the Keeper of Secrets. He will tell you everything, and explain things better than me.</p></html>