<html><p>The third part of the Revelation says that Sarnaut is a prison created by Nihaz, the God of Darkness, to restrain his sworn enemy Sarn, the God of Light.</p><p>Most of the creatures living in this world were created by Sarn, and his only goal was to use them to destroy his prison. Sarn has been craving for freedom for too long. He has been twisted and is no longer the pure entity he once was.</p></html>