<html><p>Hello! Would you like to work for the good of the Empire? I am a cartographer, and I'm putting together a detailed map of the city. Lately my work has come to a halt because of those goblins! The scoundrels are very cheeky - asking me for money for a city "pass" and threatening me.</p><p>Someone recommended that I talk with the "Black Hyenas" to solve this problem, claiming they'd be able to remove those jokers from my territory. Unfortunately, those bandits aren't much different from our bureaucrats - they're incredibly lazy!</p><p>They said to me, "You're a cartographer, you make maps, so give us a map showing where the goblins are and we'll eliminate them". Can you believe that?!</p><p>Let's do it like this - you walk around the neighborhood and find these goblins. Remember where their encampments are, tell me, and I will put them down on the map. Then I can give it to the Black Hyenas. They say that there are two groups of goblins operating here. Now go find them for me please.</p></html>