<html><p>Well, now you know... quite a lot. Not all there is to know, but what I've told you is more than enough. The vast majority of living things live long and utterly blind lives without ever learning even a tiny fraction of what you now know. For now, I have nothing more to tell you. Later, perhaps.</p><p>Now go to my faithful servant. What does he call himself? Ah, yes - the Keeper of Power... Well, that can't be helped - there is a measure of theatrics inherent to my creatures. Every single one of them believes they've been chosen by the gods!</p><p>In short, go to the Keeper of Power. It will fill you in on the details.</p></html>