<html>We're getting closer to the wormhole. We had a pretty hard time, the ship is barely holding itself together... What the hell?!<br/>...<br/>Demons! Demons attacking again! Fire in the hole! All hands on deck!!<br/>May they get devoured by the Astral, we'll have to jump into an unknown sector blindly, unprepared! May the Light save our souls!<br/>Why are you just standing there? Grab a cannon and show those astral shrimps how things are done in Siveria! We just need to get through to the wormhole, and then we're in the clear!</html>