<body>
<p>Incense can be used in a prayer that calls upon your patron to grant a special blessing. The blessing allows using Myrrh to cast Martyr's Gift/Martyr's Guidance/Martyr's Protection spells at the <tip_green>second/third/fourth</tip_green> level of patronage.</p>
<p>The blessing also decreases the duration of the Icy Grave, Hypnosis, Lethargy Potion and Debilitating Plague effects by <tip_green>70/75/80/85%</tip_green> and grants immunity to them for <tip_green>15/20/25/30/35</tip_green> seconds after being affected by them at the <tip_green>first/second/third/fourth/fifth</tip_green> level of patronage.</p>
<p><tip_grey><br>This item is stored in a bag. Consumed on use.</br></tip_grey></p>
</body>