<html><p>Have you heard the story of how one Orc got three generals drunk? Me neither. Too bad, or all my problems would be solved by now.</p><p>Let's try this. Take this keg of beer to the generals and make sure to get there while it's still cold! Carry it as quick as you can and give it to my assistant Mikhail Shapkin. I'm pretty sure that once they've had some of this, they'll be distracted for long enough that we can finish the rest of our preparations before they get too angry.</p><p>But remember - there are tons of soldier boys hanging around that won't let beer slip past them just like that. Keep your eyes open at all times! I tell you, nothing's sacred these days - not even officers' booze!</p></html>