<html><p>Look what I've received - a letter on birch bark. Written in blood, according to these bastards' custom, eh. In essence, it's a formal challenge to a duel.</p><p>Someone, undersigning as Vakula, demands to meet our... hm... 'representative' in order to solve some, hm, 'matters of controversy' once and for all. That isn't what's written here, of course, but I'm not going to utter these rude words and vulgarities.</p><p>The meeting is to take place in the remote portion of the Dead Thicket to the southeast of here. Could you use another reward? If so, meet him there and show his kind that we will not be trifled with.</p></html>