<html>Where did you get that sign?! That's the sign of our sworn enemies, damned red traitors. They call themselves Steel Claw tribe! Long time ago, we were one tribe. But there were fools who wanted equal rights. A lady and a nest for everyone, and no need to work! They wanted a stupid thing, a revolution. There was the war, an old town was burned down. Now, there are two settlements, two tribes and a never-ending war.<br/>Tell me why did you go to their settlement! You could not get the sign of Steel Claw anywhere else.</html>