<html><p>Stop! Calm down! Stop the violence!</p><p>What do you want to know? Yasker's weak spot?</p><p>Hmm... Perhaps I'm the only one who can tell you something about that.</p><p>For a very long time I've been trying to understand why Yasker hates us, the Zem. He keeps this secret safe, but I've recently discovered his secret. During our final exams one young necromancer demonstrated his abilities, and I saw how the Great Mage was avoiding the summoned creatures! You see? He hates undead, their rotten flesh, their smell... And his disgust spreads on us, too!</p><p>What a fool! Why can't he see the difference? He's got to change his attitude, or soon he will be dethroned.</p></html>