<html><p>Have you seen the stone giants? We're sure you have, we're talking about those two giant statues in the middle of Siveria - the ones with the horrible, ugly mugs. They say that they've been there since the time of the Zem civilization.</p><p>We heard that a treasure was buried not far from those giants. The legends say that they guard it with their stony gaze, but that's just rubbish! We're dying to get our hands on that treasure, but it's far too scary to go there! But we're sure you could do it, you look so strong! You should try!</p></html>