<html><p>Listen to me, stranger, for I, Kaid, never waste time. Do you think we met by chance? No. Fate itself brought you here. Fate and what you surface dwellers call a "Patron." I feel the power brimming within both you and me! And this power comes from the same source.</p><p>But my race does not believe in any "Patrons"! I chanced to hear about some of your sorcerers who died ages ago. It is said that their sparks had dissolved in the Astral and became what people now call "Patrons." But look at me! My brothers and I are endowed with the same power as you. The fact that you mastered our weapons only proves this. Now think, why would spellcasters from the surface endow underground creatures like us with what appears to be their own power? Why so silent? You don't know what to say? I don't either...</p><p>All I know is that there is a mystical power in our world. We call this power the Source. You call it Patrons. Our Source has twelve manifestations, twelve faces. You have twelve Patrons. This power gives you the ability to heal yourself, fight pain and fear, become stronger or more accurate... We cannot do these things. But with the same power we can become invisible, see what is hidden and feel what is concealed... and many things that the surface creatures couldn't even begin to fathom.</p><p>Don't let my frankness surprise you. The power of the Source has brought you here, and chose me to be the conductor of its will. I told you much of what we know. Not everything, but quite a lot! Consider it my gift to you for your valor in combat. And now we must part. Remember that our races are enemies. Should fate reunite us on the battlefield, I will not hesitate to kill you, nor will I regret it. </p></html>