<html><p>The demons continue their attempts to dislodge us from the Wild Cape. They want to regain the demonic portal that lies in the center of our camp. Demon scouts constantly land along the shore and attack anyone that ventures outside the barricade.</p><p>I have sent a request to Yasker for more troops, but at the moment it looks like we'll have to fend for ourselves. If we wait any longer, the reinforcements will find nothing but ruins when they arrive.</p><p>Go out and kill as many of the demons as you can. They should be easy to find. After securing our borders, perhaps we can begin some offensive maneuvers.</p></html>