<html><p>My platoon has been charged with the task of capturing the Site of Power in Tekyan Thicket. We must capture it before it's overtaken by the League. To help us get through the impenetrable jungle, I've decided to use a bit of magic!</p><p>I'll create a fire elemental who will burn down these trees and thus make a path to the Site of Power. I'll need your help as well, though.</p><p>Your job is to protect the elemental from predators and enemy troops. And don't forget to feed it dried branches along the way! His flame will go out and he won't be able to complete his mission if you don't.</p></html>