<html>At long last I saw the mage I owe my life to! He's a strange one. I tried to thank him, and he started waving his hands and talking ‘bout some urgent business. Ah, to heck with him!<br/>I decided to wait for the others with the Elf. Since you'll be the first to Novograd, will you do me a favor? Please visit the Gibberling Embassy in the Gibberling District and tell them my story. I'm sorry to say that my search has failed. I was not able to find the Gibberling homeland but maybe other scouts will have more luck.<br/>Thank you for everything. Losing my sisters was a serious blow, I tell you. But I will continue on my way, perhaps together with Lok, another loner like myself. Together we'll have an easier time dealing with our loss. Maybe we'll meet again one day!</html>