<html><p>After the darkness descended upon us the Elves of the House de Ardeur took refuge in the Tainted Woods. We had no problems communicating with the de Ardeurs until recently...</p><p>The fact that our communications have been interrupted worries me greatly. Please use the June ruins and check the communication beacons.</p><p>Go from beacon to beacon and you'll eventually end up at their camp. Once you get the job done, go see the head of the House de Ardeur. Good luck!</p></html>