<html><p>In the desert there lives a giant sand worm named Hai'shulud. They say he's hundreds of years old and Xadaganians, Orcs, and Arisen all live in fear of him. Only the Freeborn are able to avoid his wrath for we are wise enough to sense him before he strikes.</p><p>His lair is just to the east of Pridonsk, beneath the jaws of an ancient sea creature. Go there and bang on the giant skull. This will disrupt his rest and he'll angrily come forth from the sands.</p><p>If you are truly strong, you'll be able to defeat him and claim victory over the desert. This is your test. If you pass it, you will earn the respect of the Freeborn. Then we can talk business.</p></html>