<html><p>Do you know that ancient June were great artisans who knew all secrets of gem-crafting?</p><p>We know, for example, that they could craft an armor out of huge diamonds! Warriors in such armor were almost invulnerable.</p><p>Why am I telling you that? Because our masters are crafty enough to do something which only the June could do!</p><p>Earlier, as you know, it was possible to wear just one magic earring as two earrings could resonate or weaken each other. But now when we know June's secrets of gem-crafting our jewelers learned to craft paired earrings! Isn't it cool?</p><p>Jewelers explained their knowledge in Jeweler's Manuscripts and put them into Radiant Strongboxes which can be bought from the Item Shop for everyone to learn how to equip the second earring. I can exchange ten such manuscripts for an Expert Jeweler's Manuscript.</p></html>