<html><p>Hear ye! Hear ye! We all know that there is safety in numbers! In view of this Aidenus, the Great Mage, has issued an order that allows citizens of the League to establish guilds to solve difficult problems together. You can set up your guild right here in Novograd by speaking to the Grand Guild Master Oleg Shpilev! Free citizens of the League, unite!</p><p>He's in the first house to the left of the northern gate of Novograd. Talk to him and he'll fill you in on the rest of the details.</p></html>