We did nothing wrong, Gibberling's honor! We just wanted to help that white-winged there, above. When we climbed the elevator platform, it started moving, then it just... suddenly... went broken. And all the stones showered down! That was just creepy! But we are safe, lucky we are! That aviak there, above, the elevator keeper, went for the new stones, as these he thought were misfortuned. Oh, he has been away for so long... something might have happened!