<html><p>Wait! There's another urgent matter. Remember that amulet you had to fight for in Fiercetusk the Roughneck's arena? They've finished the tests on it but unfortunately I can't tell you anything.</p><p>One of the scientists yapped about it to someone else and now the matter has been classified as 'top secret'. We've all had to sign a non-disclosure agreement. Except you. It's time to correct that.</p><p>This came right from the top, so you don't have a choice - sign it. Naturally, your discretion will be rewarded.</p></html>