<html><p>Now it is time for the Ritual.</p><p>No, we are not going to hold it in the center of Nezebgrad. Yasker wants to keep everything in secret, right?</p><p>We also need a dragon's heart. But where can we find one?</p><p>At the same place! In the secret cave of Kirah in the past.</p><p>Veronika is waiting for you there to reward you with the gift of reincarnation.</p><p>I'll give you the things you'll need to enter. Go and find her, she's waiting.</p><p>I'll wait for our next meeting with you or with any of your incarnations.</p></html>