<html><p>What did that silly Elf say again? Hic... "Immerse half in Living Water and the other half in Dead Water..." The ideas those sculptors come up with!</p><p>Here are six pieces of amber. Go and bathe the amber in the tavern... No, why would I say that? Did I say tavern? In the Living Water!</p><p>The amber needs to be bathed in the Living Water, that's right! And near the Living Spring... Uh... There are drunken satyrs. Hic... Even I don't drink that much.</p><p>They're messing with the wrong guy now! That's right... I'm not gonna drag myself right into the satyr's claws. Hic... You're serving Ivan now, so you can go do it.</p></html>