Wingless one, listen to me now. I'll give you a bone whistle. Blow the whistle, and a squawkling will come. It's small and hungry. It gonna eat like hell! A squawker is not a parrot, it doesn't eat fruits, only meat.
Go hunting, outlander, to get meat and feed a squawkling. When a squawkling grows very big, it will love you like its parent. It'll carry you on its back up high in the sky! Then you will understand and trust our people, or even make friends with us!