<html>Quarr, Son of the Wind! Good you're here. I've brought urgent news to the war chief. It's very important. We have found the traitor, the planted chick. The same one that got away from you. We know who it is. It is the damned anarchist. They do not want good or bad government. They only want war. They think no one should tell them what to do. Tagar kual kurrakh!<br/>I will fly to the winged city for help, while Viss will stay to spy on foolish anarchista. Your help will be very useful right now. Viss is hiding in bushes. You should quietly whistle, like the wind among cliffs. He will respond like a seagull cry. Together you will easily defeat anarchists.</html>