<html>Our El Dorado attract huge crowds. Some of the folks flee, but pretty many of them stay here for a long while.<br/>This place is not made of elastic rubber! There's not enough room for everyone to sleep under shelter. So, naturally, a lot of them have to stay outside during the night time.<br/>Have you ever tried to take a nap on the bare ground? I wonder if it's even possible - it's cold, and rough, and there are ants or bugs or gods know what else. Even if you manage to fall asleep, you will surely feel battered in the morning and won't be able to work properly. Thick warm blankets are on the biggest demand here.<br/>Bring me some Rare Blankets, and the guys will be so grateful to you!</html>