Every half-hour, groups of astralonauts reinforced by mercenaries gather in the port. If you can't staff a crew for an astral flight, find the mercenary captain in the port and let them know what gear you would like to get and which role you are ready to accept - tank, medic, or fighter. The mercenaries will pick the comrades-in-arms for you. If the group is understaffed, they will provide their warriors and an equipped ship for conquering the astral depths.