<html><p>Pah! His words mean nothing! I was counting on those League religionists to remain here and fight the undead, but it looks like they're more concerned with the growing schism in their ranks.</p><p>I received a message that said they have plans to go back home to convene with the Church of Light and discuss amendments to the catechism. That could take ages! In the meantime, I'll be stuck here trying to recapture my mine from the undead on my own.</p><p>Well, Strizhov did send us a box with some soil in it. It's supposedly sacred soil and Strizhov assures me that it will help us in our struggle. Let's hope he's right!</p></html>