<html>Oh, we're in trouble... That signet belonged to our captain! Does that mean the beast gobbled him up? Holy cow, he won't be able to resurrect now! How dreadful... Goddamned beasts, it's all their fault that our crew died a final death!<br/>Help us avenge our companions. Please! Their souls must not be left unrequited. Should you find any items that belonged to the sailors, bring them to us. At least we'll know who can still resurrect and who should be given funeral rites.</html>