<html><p>He lied to me! Nomarkh Semenkare... He worships Tep! We were friends, he and I. He arrived from Igsh - a diligent and enthusiastic Prospector that didn't want to leave even an inch of the allod unexplored. I suppose I should've noticed that something wasn't quite right, though.</p><p>Take his title, for instance - Nomarkh... I often asked myself why an Arisen of such high standing would suddenly decide to become a Prospector. More often than not, the job is dirty and dangerous. It's not for men like him.</p><p>He never explained the answer. Instead, he just shut everyone out. I didn't think anything of it - we, the Arisen, carry heavy mental burdens, every last one of us. Sometimes there are things we don't want to share.</p><p>And then it all came out! He's no Prospector, he's the cultists' leader! The reason he came here was to scout out the scene and make preparations for their arrival!</p><p>He didn't even remember our friendship, how we shared everything we had, down to a ragged blanket at night. He threw me in this cage and promised me a quick death.</p><p>He's mad! This cage is too strong to be broken, but please, kill those cultists if you can. Oh, and be sure to warn Gorislav at the Prospectors' Inn about this new danger! Tell him that although Nomarkh Semenkare and I always went everywhere together, I'm no cultist! No, no!</p></html>