<html><p>We have a small problem here. You see, one of our experiments didn't go so well. The newest zombies that we made weren't up to our standards and now these rejects are shuffling all over our testing grounds.</p><p>We need to clean the place up so they don't get in the way of our other experiments. Will you do it for us? And please don't destroy good ones while you're at it! We have a shortage of materials and every successful experiment needs to be preserved.</p></html>