<html><p>A letter from Sigurd? Let's see what he wrote! Alright, he thanks you for your assistance rendered and promises to increase shipments of ore to compensate for the losses suffered during downtime!</p><p>I guess this means that you were able to save the mine and the allod from complete destruction? This is wonderful news! But, unfortunately, this joy is marred by the other things that have been happening these past few days.</p><p>Strizhov has come back, and it should be noted that the events on Coldberg have greatly affected his... hmm... his stability. He just keeps going on and on about demons, sowing discord among the clergy and the congregation! I was forced to order his excommunication.</p><p>But that doesn't mean we're letting this go, oh no! The matter demands an immediate and highly thorough investigation! We must get to the bottom of the Astral Fangs and this strange Orcish woman that has joined the demon worshippers!</p></html>